We all suffer losses.
We all are going to have highs and lows in our lives.
We can all be petrified of what the future may hold and we can all have setbacks and
doubts and pain.
That's what's going to happen in life.
But if you fight for it and you work for it and you work through it, those losses and
those setbacks and that pain will make you better.
You can drive on.
You can push through.
You can deal with unimaginable adversity as long as you keep getting up every day and
keep moving forward.
You have to make yourself better by attacking every day in spite of whatever challenges you
face, go out there, fight on and no matter what, do not give up hope.
When you get tripped up or you get knocked down, what you do is you do the best you can.
You've got to go down swinging and I'll tell you this, if you fight with all that you've
got, more often than not, you don't go down at all, you win, but you've got to make that
attitude part of your everyday life, the extra rep, the extra mile, the extra round, stand
and fight against weakness and against fear, fight back, go down swinging, give every day
everything you've got.
When you face a challenge, eat at something where you don't believe you can win.
Remember this, you have nothing to lose.
So stand up and go forward and go out in a blaze of glory, fighting with everything
you've got, every ounce of energy, every beat is sweat, every drop of blood, never give
up, over against overwhelming odds, never accept the fear, persevere, and endure until
the end.
In this situation that you're in, your life is at stake.
Your life is actually at stake right now.
What you do with your life is at stake.
You are fighting for your life every day.
The way that you live, the mark that you're going to leave, the legacy that you're going
to leave, all that is going to come back to you, that is your life and your life is
at stake right now, every day, so don't sit back and be on the defense and allow life
to happen to you.
Don't do that.
Instead, you go on the offense every day by getting up and getting after it.